https://www.colum.edu/privacy.html

Your Personal Information
Columbia College Chicago respects your privacy. We will never give, sell, rent, or share your personal information with any person or company in any way not listed here, unless compelled by law.
Cookies
We use cookies to remember if you have visited our site. You have the option of disabling or not accepting cookies by changing the preferences on your browsers. If you opt to disable cookies, you will still be able to use our website.
Remarketing
We use remarketing services from Google and other providers. These providers use cookies to remember when you have visited our site and display our ads to you on other websites. You can opt out of these cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page.
Web Analytics
We use Google Analytics and other cookie or IP address-based tools to analyze website visitor behavior and technical information for reporting and marketing purposes. The information analyzed may include any personal details you voluntarily provide through online forms. You can find more information about how Google uses data, you can also prevent Google Analytics from using your data by downloading and installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on.
Sharing
We sometimes share aggregate demographic information with our partners. This information is not connected to your personal information. We share personal information with third parties as required to process that information or provide services available on Columbia College Chicago websites. Third parties are required not to share personal information.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. We have no control over the privacy practices of sites not owned by Columbia College Chicago.
Security
Columbia College Chicago takes extensive precautions to protect your information, and we have security measures in place to protect the information under our control.
Compliance and Cooperation With Regulatory Authorities
Columbia College Chicago complies with and works with appropriate regulatory authorities to ensure compliance with all applicable laws, including the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA). Any applicable laws supersede this privacy policy.
Notification of Changes
If we change this privacy policy, we will post a notice on our site.
Small Modal
Photo Credit
Check out this behind-the-scenes look at the Wabash Arts Corridor Crawl filmed by Columbia College's The Doc Unit, an advanced production course busy creating documentaries about Columbia College life.
×
Henrietta Leavitt: Unsung Heroine in Science
Henrietta Leavitt: Unsung Heroine in Science from Columbia College Chicago on Vimeo.
×
×
×
×
